Register of the Raymond Moley papers, 1902-1971
Hoover Institution Archives
- SPEECHES, 1932-1960. (Boxes 119-143)
  - Packard Bell Electronics Address, June 8, 1960 (no text or notes) (Folder 14)
  - Illinois Chamber of Commerce Address, June 24, 1960 (Folder 15)
  - Schenectady Rotary Club Address, September 22, 1960 (no text or notes) (Folder 16)
  - Hardware Manufacturers Association Address, October 18, 1960 (Folder 17)
  - Cleveland Academy of Medicine Address, October 21, 1960 (Folder 18)
  - Barnard College Address, October 25, 1960 (Folder 19)
  - Chicago Union League Club Address, October 27, 1960 (Folder 20)
  - Ohio Republican Addresses, November 1960 (no text or notes) (Folder 21)
  - Drop Forging Association Address, November 11, 1960 (Folder 22)
  - New Orleans Members' Council Address, November 17, 1960 (Folder 23)
  - Carleton College Address, December 9, 1960 (Folder 24)
  - Cuyahoga County Republican Organization Address, February 16, 1961 (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Barnard College Recording, February 1961 (Folder 2)
  - Vermont College Address, June 4, 1961 (Folder 3)
  - Republican Associates Address, June 16, 1961 (Folder 4)
  - Governors' Conference Address, June 27, 1961 (no text or notes) (Folder 5)
  - Meet the Press broadcast, October 8, 1961 (Folder 6)
  - Cleveland Bar Association Address, November 9, 1961 (Folder 7)
  - NBC-TV Appearance, January 31, 1962 (no text or notes) (Folder 8)
  - Princeton University Address, April 12, 1962 (Folder 9)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews Address, April 17, 1962 (no text or notes) (Folder 10)
  - Kansas Chamber of Commerce Address, April 24, 1962 (Folder 11)
  - Caltech Address, May 19, 1962 (Folder 12)
  - Los Angeles Town Hall Address, May 22, 1962 (Folder 13)
  - Pomona Republican Associates Address, June 8, 1962 (Folder 14)
  - 87th Club Address, July 11, 1962 (Folder 15)
  - S.O.S. Club Address, August 15, 1962 (Folder 16)
  - New York Young Republican Club Address, September 11, 1962 (no text or notes) (Folder 17)
  - California Addresses, September 18-28, 1962 (Folder 18)
  - Omaha Address, October 16, 1962 (Folder 19)
  - Tarrytown Fortnightly Club Address, October 22, 1962 (no text or notes) (Folder 20)
  - American Mutual Insurance Alliance Address, October 30, 1962 (Folder 21)
  - Pittsburgh Chamber of Commerce Address, November 26, 1962 (Folder 22)
  - Mackay-Shields Economic Forum, December 3, 1962 (no text or notes) (Folder 23)
  - Eastside Young Republican Club Address, February 26 1963 (no text or notes) (Folder 24)
  - Republican State Chairmen Address (Washington), March 1, 1963 (Folder 25)
  - Oklahoma City G.O.P. Address, April 5, 1963 (Folder 26)
  - Pima County Republican Women Address, April 10, 1963 (Folder 27)
  - Phoenix Rotary Club Address, April 12, 1963 (Folder 28)
  - Republican Workshops of Illinois Address, May 11, 1963 (no text or notes) (Folder 29)
  - New York Academy of Medicine Meeting, June 3, 1963 (no text or notes) (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Atlanta Meetings, September 17-18, 1963 (no text or notes) (Folder 2)
  - Detroit Economic Club Address, September 23, 1963 (Folder 3)
  - Cleveland Town Hall Address, October 9, 1963 (Folder 4)
  - National Management Association Address, October 25, 1963 (Folder 5)
  - Ohio Young Republican Address, December 14, 1963 (Folder 6)
  - Chicago Publicity Club Address, February 12, 1964 (Folder 7)
  - Association of National Advertisers Address, April 7, 1964 (Folder 8)
  - Southern Young Republicans Address, April 18, 1964 (Folder 9)
  - Loretto Heights College Address, May 28, 1964 (Folder 10)
  - Grier School Address, May 31, 1964 (Folder 11)
  - San Diego Republican Associates Address, June 24, 1964 (no text or notes) (Folder 12)
  - Los Angeles Republican Associates Address, June 30, 1964 (no text or notes) (Folder 13)
  - Channel City Club Address, July 7, 1964 (no text or notes) (Folder 14)
  - California Commonwealth Club Address, July 10, 1964 (Folder 15)
  - American Bar Association Address, August 10, 1964 (Folder 16)
  - Henry George School Address, August 31, 1964 (Folder 17)
  - American Life Convention Address, October 15, 1964 (Folder 18)
  - Industrial Relations Society Address, October 22, 1964 (Folder 19)
  - Dutch Treat Club Address, October 27, 1964 (Folder 20)
  - Republican Women of Pennsylvania Address, February 9, 1966 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - ABC-TV Appearance, February 11, 1966 (no text or notes) (Folder 2)
  - Claremont College New Deal Seminar, February 23, 1966 (Folder 3)
  - ABC Appearance, May 1966 (?) (Folder 4)
  - Claremont College Address, June 5, 1966 (Folder 5)
  - Dutch Treat Club Address, November 15, 1966 (Folder 6)
  - Shippensburg State College Address, March 30, 1967 (Folder 7)
  - Harvard Address, April 12, 1967 (Folder 8)
  - Johns Hopkins University Address, April 18, 1967 (no text or notes) (Folder 9)
  - National Student Leadership Conference Address, April 22, 1967 (Folder 10)
  - Organization of American Historians Meeting, April 28, 1967 (Moley could not attend; Rosen read his comments) (comments not included) (Folder 11)
  - Warner Library Address, May 25, 1967 (Folder 12)
  - Yale Political Union Address, September 26, 1967 (Folder 13)
  - New York Address, November 8, 1967 (Folder 14)
  - BBC Interview, March 13, 1968 (no text or notes) (Folder 15)
  - Speech Association of the Eastern States Address, April 5, 1968 (no text or notes) (Folder 16)
- BIOGRAPHICAL FILE, 1910-1970 (Boxes 144-184)
  Announcements, biographical sketch, clippings, correspondence, finances, itineraries, master's thesis, notes for doctoral thesis, programs, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - General. Includes honors received, enrollment papers at Columbia University, appointment as mayor of Olmstead Falls (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Announcements and programs of speaking engagements (Folder 2)
  - Biographical sketch (Folder 3)
  - Clippings about Moley. May contain clippings about Today. See also OVERSIZE FILE
    - Undated (Folder 4)
    - 1910-1919 (Folder 5)
    - 1920-1928 (Folder 6)
    - 1929 (Folder 7-8)
    - 1930 (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - 1931 (Folder 2)
    - 1932 (Folder 3)
    - 1933 (Folder 4-6)
    - 1934 (Box 146-147)
    - 1934 (Box 148, Folder 1-2)
    - 1934 (Box 155-159)
    - 1935 (Box 148, Folder 3-5)
    - 1935 (Box 149, Folder 1-4)
    - 1935 (Box 159-162)
    - 1936 (Box 150, Folder 1-4)
    - 1936 (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - 1936 (Box 163-167)
    - 1937 (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - 1937 (Box 168-171)
    - 1938 (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - 1938 (Box 171-174)
    - 1939 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - 1939 (Box 174-176)
    - 1940 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - 1940 (Box 177-179)
    - 1941 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - 1941 (Box 179-180)
    - 1942 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - 1942 (Box 181)
    - 1943 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - 1943 (Box 182)
    - 1944 (Box 152, Folder 5-7)
    - 1945 (Box 182)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - 1948 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - 1949 (Folder 2)
    - 1950 (Folder 3)
    - 1951 (Folder 4)
    - 1952 (Folder 5)
    - 1953 (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - 1954 (Folder 2)
    - 1955 (Folder 3)
    - 1956 (Folder 4)
    - 1957 (Folder 5)
    - 1958 (Folder 6)
    - 1959-1960 (Folder 7)
    - 1960's (Folder 8)
    - 1961-1962 (Folder 9)
    - 1963-1964 (Folder 10)
    - 1965-1970 (Folder 11)
  - Doctoral thesis on the presidential campaign of 1896, started in 1914, abandoned in 1916. Preliminary notes (Box 183)
  - Finances. Includes rental agreement with Vincent Astor, book contracts (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Master's thesis, Oberlin College, 1913 (Folder 2)
  - Receivership at St. Regis Hotel (Folder 3)
  - Travel itineraries and papers. Includes correspondence about his vacation in 1946 (Folder 4)
- CLEVELAND PERIOD FILE, 1916-1923. (Boxes 184-185)
  Clippings, correspondence, proposed legislation, notes, printed materials, programs, proposals, and reports, concerning Moley's involvement with the Americanization effort and his directorship of the Cleveland Foundation, mostly having to do with crime and the administration of justice, arranged alphabetically by Moley's affiliations. See also OVERSIZE FILE
  - General
    - General (Box 184, Folder 5)
    - Clippings (Folder 6)
    - Court cases (Folder 7)
    - Legislation, proposed (Folder 8)
    - Notes (Folder 9)
    - Printed materials (Folder 10)
  - Americanization effort
    - General
      - Clippings (Folder 11)
      - Correspondence (Folder 12)
      - Legislation, proposed (Folder 13)
      - Notes (Folder 14)
      - Printed materials (Folder 15)
      - Programs for conferences and institutes for which Moley was a lecturer (Folder 16)
      - Proposals and reports by various authors (Folder 17)
    - Committees on which Moley served
      - Citizens' Bureau
        - Annual report (Folder 18)
        - Foreword to pamphlet on Czechs (Box 185, Folder 1)
        - Graduation exercises (Folder 2)
        - Minutes (Folder 3)
      - Cleveland Americanization Council (Folder 4)
      - Committee on Americanization of the Ohio Institute for Public Efficiency. Draft and final report to the Ohio Council of Social Agencies, Moley, Herbert Adolphus Miller, and Juliette Sessions, authors (Folder 5)
      - Committee on Immigration and Emigration. Minutes (Folder 6)
      - Ohio State Council of Defense (Folder 7)
      - State Department of Education, Division of Americanization
        - General. Includes programs for Teachers' Training Institute, Moley, lecturer (Folder 8)
        - Report on federal leadership and legislation (Folder 9)
    - Proposal for federal legislation on immigration (Folder 10)
  - Cleveland Foundation, Moley, Director
    - General
      - Announcements of meetings to discuss survey results (Folder 11)
      - Clippings (Folder 12)
      - Correspondence (Folder 13)
      - Finances (Folder 14)
      - Notes concerning the policy of the Cleveland Foundation (Folder 15)
    - Annual reports
      - 1921 (Folder 16)
      - 1923 (Folder 17)
    - Evaluations of implementation of survey suggestions
      - Five-year reports on the crime survey, Moley, Carlton K. Matson, unknown, authors, 1926. Typescript and photocopies (Folder 18)
      - Report on the recreation survey, n.d. Typescript (Folder 19)
    - Proposals for Cleveland Foundation projects, various subjects (Folder 20)
    - Publications of the Cleveland Foundation, by Moley
      - An Outline of the Cleveland Crime Survey, 1922. Printed copy (Folder 21)
      - A Review of the Surveys of the Cleveland Foundation, 1923. Printed copy (Folder 22)
  - Subject file
    - Cleveland Association of Criminal Justice, eighth annual meeting (Folder 23)
    - County jail, grand jury investigation (Folder 24)
    - Radicals (Folder 25)
  - Western Reserve University. Faculty appointment, general papers (Folder 26)
- COLUMBIA PERIOD FILE, 1923-1933. (Boxes 185-209)
  Clippings, correspondence, course materials, curricula, journals, memoranda, minutes, notes, pamphlets, printed materials, proposals, proposed legislation, reports, and speeches and writings relating to Moley's involvement with educational institutions, commissions, committees, conferences, surveys, reports, and investigations, mostly having to do with crime and the administration of justice, arranged by project. See also CORRESPONDENCE FILE and SPEECHES AND WRITINGS
  - General
    - General. Includes memoranda and correspondence (Box 185, Folder 27)
    - Prosecution. Notes and data (Folder 28)
  - Columbia University, Columbia Law School, and Barnard University, faculty appointment, 1923-1931
    - General
      - Clippings (Folder 29)
      - Notes (Folder 30)
      - Notes (Box 186, Folder 1-2)
      - Printed matter (Folder 3-4)
      - Printed matter (Box 187, Folder 1-2)
    - Administrative papers
      - General (Folder 3)
      - Committee on Instruction (Folder 4)
      - Committee records (Folder 5)
      - Correspondence with Dean Gildersleeve (Folder 6)
      - Law School curriculum (Folder 7)
      - Memoranda about a grant proposal (Folder 8)
      - National Conference on the Science of Politics, September 7-11, 1925. Includes printed material, correspondence, notes, memoranda (Folder 9)
      - "The Objectives of the School of Law of Columbia University," n.d. Typescript (Folder 10)
      - Social Science committee (Folder 11)
    - Course materials
      - General
        - Exams (Folder 12)
        - Grade book (Folder 13)
        - Hand-outs (Folder 14)
        - Lectures. Also see specific courses (Box 188, Folder 1)
        - Student papers (Folder 2-3)
      - Courses
        - Principles of Politics (Folder 4)
        - Theory and Practice of Politics. Includes administrative notes, etc. (Folder 5)
        - Public Law 161-162 (Folder 6)
        - Government 2, "Public Opinion" (Folder 7)
        - Government 7-8
          - General
            - Exams (Folder 8)
            - Lectures and notes (Folder 9)
          - "American Political Life" (Folder 189)
            - Hand-outs (Folder 1)
            - Lectures, arranged chronologically
              - 1933 (Folder 2)
              - 1934 (Folder 3-5)
              - 1935 (Folder 6)
          - "Great American Political Personalities"
            - Notes for lectures on Theodore Roosevelt (Folder 7)
            - Student papers (Box 190, Folder 1)
            - Subject file
              - Death of politicians (Folder 2-3)
              - Pocket veto (Folder 4)
              - Political theories (Folder 5)
              - President (Folder 6)
              - President's cabinet, 1929 (Folder 7)
              - Presidential Third Term (Box 191, Folder 1)
              - Controversy
              - Removal power (Folder 2)
              - Borah, William E. (Folder 3)
              - Bryan, William Jennings (Folder 4)
              - Cannon, Joseph (Folder 5)
              - Cleveland, Grover (Folder 6)
              - Coolidge, Calvin (Folder 7)
              - Curtis, Charles (Folder 8)
              - Dawes, Charles (Folder 9)
              - Debs, Eugene Victor (Box 192, Folder 1)
              - Hanna, Mark (Folder 2)
              - Hearst, William Randolph (Folder 3)
              - Hague, Frank (Folder 4-5)
              - Hoover, Herbert (Folder 6)
              - House, Colonel Edward M. (Folder 7)
              - Hughes, Charles E. (Folder 8)
              - Hylan, John (Folder 9)
              - Jackson, Andrew (Folder 10)
              - LaFollette, Robert M. (Box 193, Folder 1)
              - Lincoln, Abraham (Folder 2)
              - Lowden, Frank O. (Folder 3)
              - Osborne, Thomas M. (Folder 4)
              - Raskob, John J. (Folder 5)
              - Reed, James A. (Folder 6)
              - Ritchie, Albert C. (Folder 7)
              - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Folder 8)
              - Roosevelt, Theodore (Folder 9)
              - Sinclair, Harry Ford (Folder 10)
              - Smith, Alfred E. (Folder 11)
              - Smith, Alfred E. (Box 194, Folder 1)
              - Taft, William Howard (Folder 2)
              - Thompson, William Hale (Folder 3)
              - Tilden, Samuel J. (Folder 4)
              - Walker, James J. (Folder 5)
              - Walsh, Thomas J. (Folder 6)
              - Weed, Thurlow (Folder 7)
              - Wilson, Woodrow (Folder 8)
        - Government 117-118 (Box 195)
          - Exams and course outline (Folder 1)
          - Lectures (Folder 2-3)
    - Subject file
      - Agriculture (Folder 4)
      - Associated Press (Folder 5)
      - Bias and propaganda (Folder 6)
      - British parties (Folder 7)
      - Campaigns (Folder 8)
      - Chicago election, 1927 (Folder 9)
      - Court of Criminal Appeals (Folder 10)
      - Court of General Sessions (Folder 11)
      - Foreign language press (Folder 12)
      - Gilded age (Box 196, Folder 1)
      - Governmental research (Folder 2)
      - History of American parties
        - Early Republican Party (Folder 3)
        - Jeffersonian democracy (Folder 4)
        - Democratic revolution (Folder 5)
        - Wilsonism (Folder 6)
        - Progressivism (Folder 7)
        - Federalist system (Folder 8)
        - Normalcy (Folder 9)
        - 1896, the great divide (Folder 10)
      - History of the press to 1880 (Folder 11)
      - Immigration (Folder 12)
      - Individualization in the treatment of offenders. Conference papers (Folder 13)
      - Organizations with political purposes
        - Religion (Folder 14)
        - Labor (Box 197, Folder 1)
        - Anti-Saloon League (Folder 2)
      - Police (Folder 3)
      - Political corruption (Folder 4)
      - Political parties - National conventions (Folder 5)
      - Presidential campaign, 1928 (Folder 6)
      - Press (Folder 7)
      - Public relations and propaganda (Folder 8)
      - Radio (Folder 9)
  - Commission to study proposal for a parole court, appointed by Governer Franklin D. Roosevelt, January-February 1930
    - Background materials
      - Clippings (Folder 10)
      - Notes (Folder 11)
      - Pamphlets and printed material (Folder 12)
    - Internal papers
      - General (Folder 13)
      - Legislation. Includes correspondence, suggested revisions by Moley (Folder 14)
      - Minutes, January 1930 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Report
      - Printed copy, February 5, 1930 (Folder 2)
      - Appendix D (Folder 3)
    - Subject file
      - Constitution and the corrections system (Folder 4)
      - New York Crime Commission (Folder 5)
      - Prison system, New York State. Address by Lieutenant Governor Herbert H. Lehman, January 26, 1930 (Folder 6)
  - Committee on the Administration of Justice, New York State, 1928-1933. Moley was Research Director, 1931-1933
    - Correspondence
      - General. In shorthand (Folder 7)
      - Committee members. Includes Charles Burdick, Leonard Saxe, Harry D. Nims, George R. Fearon, Walter Westall, John L. Buckley (Folder 8)
      - Other (Folder 9)
      - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Folder 10)
    - Establishment of the committee
      - General
        - Clippings (Folder 11)
        - Notes (Folder 12)
        - Printed material and press release (Folder 13)
      - Speeches and writings
        - Campaign speech on administration of justice, n.d. Partial draft, typescript (Folder 14)
        - Speeches for Franklin D. Roosevelt on administration of justice, October 30, 1928 and n.d. Holograph, typescript and press release (Folder 15)
        - "Justice in Our Courts: Shall We Have a State Commission to Report on its Administration?" written by Moley for John Knight, Jan. 1930. Holograph, typescript and printed (Folder 16)
    - Internal papers
      - Background materials (Folder 17)
      - List of studies under the auspices of the commission (Folder 18)
      - Legislation, proposed (Box 199, Folder 1)
      - Memoranda and proposals (Folder 2)
      - Minutes, September 30, 1931 (Folder 3)
      - Notes. Holograph (Folder 4)
      - Proposed Plan of Organization and Procedure. Includes work by Moley and Herman Oliphant. Holograph and typescript (Folder 5)
    - Reports
      - Preliminary report, 1932
        - Draft, Moley author? Typescript (Folder 6)
        - Summary. Typescript (Folder 7)
        - Final. Printed copy (Folder 8)
      - General. Printed matter, 1934 (Folder 9)
      - Report and recommendation on perjury, n.d. Typescript (Folder 10)
  - Committee on the Administration of Justice (Contd.)
    - Sub-committee on the Simplification of the Penal Code
      - Crimes of a political nature, preliminary report, by Robert E. Cushman, April 1932. Typescript and correspondence (Folder 11)
      - "Offenses Against the State Government and its Administration" by Robert E. Cushman, memorandum, June 1932. Typescript (Folder 12)
      - Preliminary report on simplification of penal code, written by John MacDonald, June 1932. Typescript (Folder 13)
    - Subject file
      - General (Folder 14)
      - Court of General Sessions (Folder 15)
      - Criminal law (Folder 16)
      - History of the administration of justice, by state (Folder 17-18)
      - Municipal court (Folder 19)
      - Sentencing powers (Folder 20)
      - Supreme Court (Box 200, Folder 1)
      - Supreme Court justices (Folder 2)
  - Committee on a Preliminary Survey of Research on Crime and Criminal Justice for the Social Science Research Council, 1926-1928?
    - General (Folder 3)
    - "The Current Status of Research in Criminal Law Administration". Notes, holograph and typescript drafts (Folder 4)
    - Internal papers. Includes reports, finances, memoranda, survey suggestions, minutes (Folder 5)
  - Committee on Survey of the Chicago Crime Commission, 1926-1931?
    - Correspondence (Folder 6)
    - Background material
      - General (Folder 7)
      - Bulletin of the Chicago Crime Commission. Includes annual reports (Folder 8)
      - Clippings (Folder 9)
      - Criminal Justice, Journal of the Chicago Crime Commission (Folder 10)
    - Internal papers
      - General (Folder 11)
      - Materials assembled by the Operating Director, Henry Barrett Chamberlin (Folder 12)
      - Minutes (Folder 13)
    - Reports
      - By Moley
        - Notes (Folder 14)
        - Draft, n.d. Typescript (Box 201, Folder 1)
        - Typescript copy (Folder 2)
      - By Lashly, Arthur V. (Folder 3)
      - Comparison of the two reports (Folder 4)
    - Subject file
      - General (Folder 5)
      - Bail (Folder 6)
      - Chief justice (Folder 7)
      - Judicial personnel (Folder 8)
      - Illinois and crime. Address by Frank Joseph Loesch to the Illinois Society for Mental Hygiene (Folder 9)
      - Legal basis of the court (Folder 10)
      - Ordinary criminal branches (Folder 11)
      - Prosecution and defense (Folder 12)
      - Special courts (Folder 13)
  - Conference for designing a uniform offense classification for criminal statistics, called by the Federal Bureau of Investigation and the Bureau of the Census, 1931-1932
    - Background materials (Folder 14)
    - Internal papers. Includes letters, memoranda, committee roster (Folder 15)
    - Pamphlet for the American Bar Association based on the classification designed by the conference, written by L.C. Marshall. Typescript (Folder 16)
    - Proposal
      - Drafts (Folder 17)
      - Final copy (Folder 18)
  - Crime Commission of New York State, 1926-1931. See also SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, "An Analysis of the Work and Accomplishments of the Crime Commission of New York State," August 1928 and SUBJECT FILE, Crime Commission of New York - Reports
    - Correspondence
      - General (Folder 19)
      - Baumes, Caleb H. (Folder 20)
      - Gehlke, G.E. (Folder 21)
      - Hoey, Jane (Folder 22)
      - Knight, John (Folder 23)
      - Smith, Herbert L. (Folder 24)
      - Van Aernem, Harold N. (Folder 25)
      - Willbach, Harry (Folder 26)
    - Internal papers
      - General (Folder 27)
      - Finances (Folder 28)
      - Legislation, proposed (Folder 29)
    - Public hearings
      - 1926 June 11-November 23 (Folder 30)
      - 1926 Nov. 9-10. Toronto and Kingston, Canada (Folder 31)
      - 1926 Nov. 11. Montreal, Canada (Folder 32)
      - 1926. Digest of Hearings: Buffalo, Rochester, New York, Elmira (Box 202, Folder 1)
    - Sub-Commission on Causes and Effects of Crime
      - Background materials (Folder 2)
      - Data (Folder 3)
      - Notes and correspondence (Folder 4)
      - Outline of work and tentative budget (Folder 5)
      - Survey of causes of crime (Folder 6)
      - Drafts of report on causes of crime. Includes "Popular Misconceptions Concerning Crime" by Moley. Typescript (Folder 7)
    - Sub-Commission on Police
      - Draft of questionnaires (Folder 8)
      - Notes on the committee by Moley (Folder 9)
      - Preliminary Report: Questionnaire and Suggestions, December 6, 1926. Typescript (Folder 10)
    - Sub-Commission on Statistics